<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="home_second">Home Second</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="menu_walk">Walk Trail</string>
    <string name="menu_beach">Beach</string>
    <string name="menu_city">City</string>
    <string name="menu_show">Show</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About us</string>
    <string name="tour_guide_app">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="info_chaacho_com">info@chaacho.com</string>
    <string name="text_title_about">About Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="text_home">Welcome to Tenerife</string>
    <string name="text_about">Tour Guide App: Is a project developed by: Herbert Rodríguez.\n Is the
        project #6 from the Nanodegree Basic Android Developer at Udacity. \n\n
Tenerife is the chosen city. It is the place where I reside. In this app you can see a small number
        of interesting and very varied sites. \n\n
From the mountain, through the city to the beach and an entertainment area. \n\n
I hope you visit Tenerife a spectacular site. \n\n For more info keep in touch at info@chaacho.com</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_tenerife">Welcome to Tenerife</string>
    <string name="short_description">Short Description</string>
    <string name="tvName">Name</string>
    <string name="image_of_activity">Image of Activity</string>
    <string name="imageHeader">Image Header Logo</string>
    <string name="elduque">El Duque \nLocation:Adeje"</string>
    <string name="elduque_des">Everything we have to say in favor of El Duque Beach is in the image.
                         The beach is located in the municipality of Adeje, in the Southwest, it is
                        390 m long and has one bad thing: it is so beautiful that it gets crowded.</string>
    <string name="teresitas">Las Teresitas</string>
    <string name="teresitas_descr">Las Teresitas beach is three times bigger than El Duque beach (1,300
                        m), it is in the town of San Andrés (municipality of Santa Cruz de Tenerife)
                         and it has a medium degree of occupation, neither high nor low. In its favor,
                        being the Canary Islands so touristy, is the fact that it is not embedded in a
                        marsh of buildings, but isolated. You have to go.</string>
    <string name="gigantes">De los Gigantes\nLocation:Los Gigantes</string>
    <string name="gigantes_desc">Los Gigantes accidentally dispose of themselves between the terms of
                        Buenavista del Norte and Santiago del Teide. Some cliffs open and show inlets
                        and small beaches that are a joy. For example, this one, near Puerto de Los
                        Gigantes: nice, pretty.</string>
    <string name="lalaguna">City La Laguna \nLa Laguna.</string>
    <string name="lalaguna_desc">The old capital of Tenerife and the former headquarters of the general
                         captaincy of the Canary Islands, something like the de facto capital of the
                         Canary archipelago; the only city declared a World Heritage Site by UNESCO
                         in the Canary Islands; the model for all Spanish colonial cities in the
                         New World. La Laguna is the jewel in the crown of the cultural heritage
                        of the north of Tenerife and the entire island.</string>
    <string name="la_orotava">City of La Orotava \n La Orotava</string>
    <string name="la_orotava_descr">The town of La Orotava is another essential in the north of Tenerife.
                        It was the first town that became independent from La Laguna and obtained
                        the title of town, hence its proud inhabitants continue to be called
                        \"villeros\". Already from the road, the red dome of the church of La
                        Concepción warns you that you are approaching a city with character.,</string>
    <string name="puerto_cruz">Urban Musseum \nPuerto de la Cruz.</string>
    <string name="puerto_cruz_descr">When we arrived in Puerto de la Cruz we had no idea that we would
                        find a large open-air museum of urban art in its fishing neighborhood,
                        La Ranilla. The Puerto Street Art project surprised us and we liked it so
                        much that we dedicated an entire article to it.</string>
    <string name="icod_vinos">"City of Icod de los Vinos \nIcod de los Vinos</string>
    <string name="icod_vinos_descr">The historic center of Icod de los Vinos is another one worth a visit,
                        although the part that is best preserved is much smaller, basically the one
                        that surrounds the Plaza de la Pila.</string>
    <string name="arona">Arona en Colores \nCity: Las Galletas</string>
    <string name="arona_descr">Arona in colors is a multicolored urban party. It will be held this
                         Saturday June 14 from 10 a.m. to 12 p.m.</string>
    <string name="noche_azul">Noche Azul \nCity: Los Cristianos.</string>
    <string name="noche_azul_desc">The blue night returns to Los Cristianos, on August 22 the night will
                        be filled with light, music, fireworks, organizes the Christian Town Hall,
                        municipality of Arona.</string>
    <string name="galletas">Arona en colores\nCity: Las Galletas</string>
    <string name="galletas_descr">Arona in colors arrives at the Cookies. Multicolor Urban Party.
                        Music and street events, you can\'t miss it. Organized by the City Council
        of Arona, Los Cristianos. We wait for you
                        this coming Saturday June 15.</string>
    <string name="gala">Gala Solidaria \nCity:Los Cristianos</string>
    <string name="gala_descr">Solidarity gala, a child a meal a book.
                        Participate in this musical event tribute to the music of all time, bolero
                        rock, pop, dance. Infanta Leonor Auditorium.
                        Organized by Rotary Club Tenerife Sur.</string>

</resources>
